After ruining your face,
I'll see who else you can seduce.
Master,
what are you going to do?
Don't move,
or I'll
cut your face,
and it'll be too late.
Shen Suhe,
it's useless to take me as hostage.
His Highness has gone to confiscate your property.
Shut up.
I'll deal with you later.
Open the door.
Don't move.
This...
Get me a horse.
The fastest one.
Go.
Tell His Majesty
that your father has been colluding with Xiao Wei for years.
Then
I'll spare your life.
My father
never had any private dealings
with any general on the border.
Brother.
Sister.
Let's go.
Brother.
You naughty girl.
How dare you run out?
Mu Jinghao.
Shen Suhe.
How dare you look at me like this?
You're so bold.
Believe it or not, I'll kill you now.
Mu Jinghao.
You must have tried
to kill me for many times.
Shouldn't you be killed?
Chuchu and I are childhood sweethearts,
but you broke us up.
I should have been the Crown Prince,
but your father prevented me.
You should be
killed!
I broke you up?
When His Majesty arranged the marriage,
you had the chance to refuse,
but you agreed happily
to please your father.
You instigated those officials
to submit memorials for the Crown Prince
for hundreds of times, but never got a response.
Your Majesty is in his prime,
and has no intention of appointing a Crown Prince.
Even if my father wasn't there,
he would have chosen another official to counterbalance you.
Mu Jinghao,
it's your own weakness
that you dare not resist your father.
Yet you blame all your grievances
on my father.
Do you really hate my father?
What you hate
is the emperor
who crushed you
with the technique of balance.
What you hate
is that you have seen through everything,
but you don't even have the courage to overturn the chessboard.
You are just a marionette.
Even your hatred
to hate, but have to borrow others' heads as a sheath.
You,
even if you put on this robe,
you can't cover the stench in your bones.
My father
would rather die
than associate with a worm like you,
who gnaws at the bones,
harming loyal ministers and generals.
Shut up!
Shen Suhe,
I'll kill you now!
You set me up to be attacked with my mom,
and when it didn't work,
you poisoned my mom to death.
You even tried to make me foolish
to frame my dad
and the whole mansion.
I'm afraid that General Xiao's death
is also your fault.
Mu Jinghao,
if I deserve to die,
you deserve to be cut into pieces.
You dare to slander the Prince.
According to the law,
I can kill you right now.
Come on.
You know best
if I slandered him.
Can two secret letters
really make everything perfect?
My father hasn't been sentenced to death,
because Your Majesty is suspicious.
Mu Jinghao,
I should have sent you to hell
for the deep hatred.
But since I have the chance
to rewrite my destiny,
I want more than just killing you.
Now Your Majesty hasn't issued a decree.
Although my father is in prison,
he hasn't been dismissed.
He's still the Prime Minister.
And I'm
the princess consort appointed by His Majesty.
If you dare to hurt the Prime Minister's Residence,
aren't you afraid
of being charged with deceiving the Emperor?
I never realized
that the Prime Minister's legitimate daughter
is actually a complete lunatic.
Don't you want to know
what else a lunatic would do?
Don't think that the destruction of the pharmacy
means I can't find evidence
of your poisoning me and my mother.
If His Majesty finds out about this,
will he still trust you?
So it was you who broke in that day.
If anyone in the mansion
gets hurt today,
I can guarantee
that within half a moment,
this will reach the palace.
Your Highness.
We did find quite a bit of evidence
against you.
We need to destroy them now.
Or the Imperial Guards will
come and take them away.
Watch these two people.
Don't let them die.
If they have any ideas,
just take them back to the mansion.
Yes, sir.
Brother.
It's you.
Princess Consort.
How are you?
Young Master Lou.
Where is this place?
Don't worry.
It's safe here.
Where's my brother?
What did you do to him?
He's badly injured
and unconscious.
I want to see him.
You can't see him now,
but I assure you,
he's safe.
Then why did you bring me here?
What do you want from me?
Do you remember
our agreement?
Now it's time to fulfill your promise.
You want to investigate
the truth of Xiao Wei's treason.
How did you know?
These days,
I've been thinking
why you keep saving me
selflessly.
Yesterday,
you risked exposing yourself
to save me and my brother.
I think
you're afraid the Second Prince would destroy the evidence.
General Xiao Wei is dead.
If the PM's Residence is attacked,
the truth of this matter
will never be known to the world.
Since we share the same goal,
why not cooperate?
Cooperate?
Are you so sure your father is innocent?
I can assure you with my life.
My father is loyal and honest.
He would never do anything treasonous.
He must have been framed by the Second Prince.
I will investigate your father's matter.
But you can't even protect yourself now.
Why should I cooperate with you?
As long as I am still the Princess Consort of Rui,
I have the chance to find the Second Prince's crimes.
That's ridiculous.
Yesterday, the Second Prince
almost killed you.
Do you dare to go back to Prince Rui's Mansion?
I've died several times.
I don't care about this.
How about that?
Do you want to cooperate?
Now your father is in prison.
In the whole Kyoto,
who dares to go against the Second Prince?
Are you really so foolish as to think
that the Emperor will back you up?
That's his own son.
Even if no one else dares,
there is one person who will dare.
Do you know
His Majesty has a brother,
Prince Yu who left the capital eight years ago?
The world knows Prince Yu left eight years ago.
and said he would never return to the capital.
But few people know that
in fact,
he privately raised many shadow guards.
It seems you have already guessed my identity.
You must be one of the shadow guards he raised.
How did you find out?
The mother of Prince Yu, Consort Dowager Li,
is in seclusion at Lingguo Temple.
You
should be the shadow guard
left by Prince Yu to protect Consort Dowager Li.
I also know that
The Imperial Consort Dowager has a hidden waist-abdomen illness.
Every June and December,
the prince will send a caravan
to secretly deliver medicine to Consort Dowager Li.
After the Imperial Consort Dowager entered Lingguo Temple,
even your father couldn't see her.
How did you meet her?
How do you know all this?
Consort Dowager Li
once saved my life.
She told me herself.
Tell me the truth.
I'm telling the truth.
I also know
that Consort Dowager Li has half of a jade pendant,
and Prince Yu has the other half.
If you don't believe me,
you can take me to confront her at any time.
But now,
my brother and I have been away for a night.
The Second Prince
will put a charge of
fleeing in fear of punishment on us.
Then my father's situation will be more difficult.
My brother's life is in your hands.
I won't lie to you.
Fine.
I'll trust you again.
Cooperate.
I trusted you so much.
But you can't even keep an eye on a person.
Are you serious about looking for her?
She is a weak woman,
with a brother who is half dead.
Where can she go?
Your Highness, calm down.
Do you remember
two people sneaked into the Great Apricot Pharmacy that day?
One of them is the princess consort.
Then the other person
must be the one who has been helping us in secret.
Shen Suhe is smart,
but she can't escape from the mansion alone.
She knows my secret.
Before my father executes Shen Yi,
I can't let her die.
Your Highness,
Prime Minister Shen is now in prison,
but his children
disappeared before the Imperial Guards searched the house.
This proves that
there is something wrong with the mansion.
You took Shen Suhe out of the mansion
to protect her.
Why did you send her back to Prince Rui's Mansion?
The Second Prince is capricious.
He might do something outrageous.
Look.
It's all in writing.
Isn't Prince Rui's Mansion here?
Why is she going there?
Send more people to follow her.
Unless her life is in danger,
don't take any action.
I'll go to my mother.
This figure
looks so familiar.
Thank you for seeing me.
You don't need to
say that.
I believe in my teacher.
He must have been set up
by someone else.
I heard last night
that you and Young Master Shen were missing.
I thought something had happened to you.
Glad you're safe.
Don't worry, Zhao.
My brother and I are both safe.
I took the risk to come to you
to ask
what happened to my father.
Why did His Majesty suddenly punish him?
I don't know what happened.
I only know that
before General Xiao was arrested,
Qianzhi had a long secret talk with father.
It's said that he gave father a secret letter.
It was written by Xiao Wei himself.
It's about the defeat in the war with the enemy.
It seems to mention your father.
A letter?
Father was so angry that
he sentenced General Xiao to death immediately.
But there's no other evidence
to prove the teacher's guilt
except that secret letter.
To balance the situation at court,
the Emperor shouldn't deal with him for now.
As for you,
Qian is now eyeing the Prime Minister's Residence.
Why don't I find a safe place for you
to avoid risks?
That's why
I must return to Prince Rui's Mansion
to find the evidence of his framing of my father.
If you go back now,
wouldn't you be walking into a trap?
It's too dangerous.
What about your brother?
I have already found a safe place
for him to recover.
The Second Prince won't find him.
There are others helping you.
He...
Who would still be willing to help us?
Now that the Prime Minister's Residence has fallen on hard times,
no one is willing to lend a hand.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't risk coming to see you.
So what do you want me to do to help you?
Your Highness is the adopted son of the Empress.
I want you to go to the Empress
and ask the Emperor for a royal decree.
Imperial Edict?
Princess Consort,
thank you for sending me back.
As for Empress,
I'm counting on you.
Don't worry.
I'll do my best.
But can you really handle it
all by yourself?
Don't worry.
Since I dare to come back,
I must have a way to deal with it.
Alright.
If
you have any difficulties,
remember to tell me.
Shen Suhe,
you dare to come back.
This is the Prince Rui's Mansion,
and I am still the Princess Consort of Rui.
I'm not afraid to come back to my home.
Where are you hiding Shen Subai?
I want to ask you the same question.
Where did you take my brother?
How dare you frame me!
You killed one of my guards last night.
Where are you hiding my brother?
Who's helping you from behind?
You just said my brother is missing.
But yesterday,
you stormed into the PM's Mansion with guards.
The people around saw it all.
I wonder if you took my brother away
to kill him in advance
or for some other purpose.
Shen Suhe,
you are a stubborn person.
Your father has been imprisoned.
You're no longer the legitimate daughter of the Prime Minister.
Who do you think you are?
Who am I?
I'm the Princess Consort of Rui
who was married to you by the Emperor.
If you hurt me,
you'll disobey His Majesty.
He will hold you accountable.
Don't think you can't be punished
by mentioning my father.
At least,
you are
dying to kill me,
but you can't, right?
From now on,
you must follow Princess Consort Rui.
Yes.
I'll wait outside.
Why are you here?
What?
Do I need to inform you in advance
if I want to see you now?
You know I didn't mean that.
Prime Minister Shen has been put in prison.
Why do you still keep Shen Suhe in the mansion?
As long as she is my princess consort,
she has the right to live in the mansion.
You promised me that
you would kick her out
once the Prime Minister was overthrown.
Are you going to break your promise?
Chuchu, stop making a fuss.
The Emperor has only detained the Prime Minister
for interrogation.
How can I kick her out
at this juncture?
I don't care.
I don't want to see her now.
Your Highness, you don't even know
how she treated me yesterday.
She almost killed me yesterday.
If it weren't for you yesterday,
how could she have left the mansion?
Do you know
that because of your impulsiveness,
you ruined my big plan?
I...
I didn't mean to.
All right.
Go back and rest.
I have something to deal with.
Your Highness.
Secondary consort.